This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
I'm so full, I think I'm gonna puff!
I think I just gained ten pounds!
Navy food sure beats bread and water!
Bread? Ha! We were lucky to eat dirt back there!
Good thing our hero came!
Good forever on your deck, Captain Buggy! Thank you!
No problem, lads! You're all very welcome!
So, how much longer before we get there, Jinbei?
What? Hmm?
The what-me, you turd!
When are we gonna arrive at Navy HQ?
I'm ready to throw down and show those damn dirtbags who's boss!
What an inspirational attitude!
I know, I can't stop shaking!
The seven warlords who sold their souls to the world government
and those three admirals!
They're no match for the likes of us, are they men?
That's right!
You should be the next king of the pirates, Captain Buggy!
Cause you're doing just what Gold Roger would do!
A special retrospective before Marineford!
The three Navy Admirals come together!
Meanwhile, at Navy Headquarters in Marineford...
May we enter!
Pardon us, but it's time!
We're going to need you to follow us down to the harbor right away!
Without First Son of the Sea Jinbei, who is with Luffy,
and Marshal D. Teach, who has burst into Impel Down,
five of the seven warlords are about to leave Marie Joie.
Among them is the infamous Boa Hancock,
waiting in silence after her stop at Impel Down.
Four of these five individuals have had dealings with the Straw Hat Pirates in the past.
White Bits nothing but a tired old geezer,
and look at the lot of you.
Beside yourselves with fear.
What's the big rush?
We still have three hours before the execution.
That's true, but I'm afraid we have to be prepared for any contingency, sir.
That's true.
Now suffer the Ursa shock.
I see you survived, Roro Noah.
If you could take a vacation, where is it you'd like to go?
I'll protect you, even if it costs me my life!
Damn you!
Someone help me!
Robin!
Loofy!
You and I will never meet again.
Farewell, Striad.
Can't wait to get your hands dirty, huh?
Creepy as usual, I see.
Dracule Mihawk, AKA Hawkeye Mihawk.
That's...
That's him.
That man is...
Hawkeye Mihawk.
I set sail for only one reason.
To meet you.
And what is your goal?
To beat you.
How foolish.
Tiger!
Trap!
Sir, state your name.
I am Roan-O-Zoro.
I'll remember it.
No one as strong as you has come around in quite some time.
So as a swordsman's courtesy, I'll use the world's strongest black sword to finish you.
Three sword style secret technique!
Five!
Three thousand words!
But why?
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame.
Fine.
SORROOOOO!
You shouldn't rush these things, young man.
There's nothing to be upset about.
Your friend will live.
It's still far too early for you to die.
My name is Hawkeye Mihawk.
You're strong, but there is much for you to learn.
No matter how many years it takes, I will hold this title as the greatest in the world and wait for you.
Until that day, you must hone your skills.
Then, seek me out, Ro-Ro-Noah-Zoro!
All right, I'm coming.
Don't suppose I'd want to miss this.
Might be a good chance to steal some more powerful shadows and corpses, after all.
If any of Ace's little buddies try anything, it'll be an all-you-can-eat buffet for me.
Gecko Maria
Now, every last shadow in Thriller Bark come to me and become my power.
Shadows has gone!
GeckoBoy
We will all fight!
Grunt!
We will turn to our fight.
I call that one the black box!
Dammit, you dropped me!
I'll crush you!
Consider this your punishment!
Sorry, but Mr. Doflamingo and Ms. Hancock, you must hurry!
Or what, little man?
Who are you to give me orders?
Or Hancock.
The guilty thoughts swimming in your hearts shall turn your flesh to stone.
Love, love, beam.
I got it!
Peace!
Actually, you make me sick!
Stay strong, sister!
This simply cannot be happening!
There's no man alive that can resist my allure, it's just not possible!
So long as that man exists in this world, I shall never know peace again!
Medusa here!
Eight-headed serpent!
Salamander!
Now come, go!
And...
badly!
He can't be.
You'd rather die than let people see this thing on your back, right?
Like I said, don't move.
Luffy, please be safe.
This is the only one of the seven warlords of the sea who has never met Luffy or his crew.
Don Quixote do Flamingo.
No more!
I'm begging you!
Why are you making me do this?
You've really let me down, and I've got zero tolerance for useless punks like you.
No, not again!
My body's moving on its own!
I can't control it!
Please!
No!
Please...
Just give me one more chance to set things right.
I swear we'll loyally follow your every command.
What a touching sentiment.
Such genuine loyalty.
But...
I still have no use for you.
Doflamingo!
The beginning is upon us.
I suggest you prepare.
We're drawing close to a new world in which only true pirates can survive.
The weak should run while they still can, or be swept away by the tides of time,
as they roll back to reveal a new era of champions.
The extent of his strength is yet unknown.
The end.
There is another figure of interest at Navy headquarters.
One who's under the command of Fleet Admiral Sengoku.
Sorry to wake you, but we really need to get moving, Admiral.
I'm up. It's already time for lunch, is it?
Admiral Aokiji.
Ice Age.
The sea. It's... frozen.
This is the power of a Navy Headquarters Admiral.
You have some very loyal friends, but you will never change, Nico Robin.
No. That's not true.
Robin! Get away from him! Watch out!
You bastard!
Stop yelling. If you thaw her out carefully, she'll live.
However, her body is extremely fragile, so you'll need to handle her with care.
If she breaks, she'll die.
For example, if I were to smash her apart...
That was close.
What in the hell are you doing?
Usopp! Chop her! Quick! Take Robin and run back to the ship! Thaw her out and keep her safe!
You're right! You got it, Captain!
You're not glassed with this crew!
Wait! Nobody attack him!
Stay back and don't interfere. I'm gonna fight him one-on-one.
What do you say? The two of us can settle this on our own!
Fine by me. But since I don't have a ship to take you back, then I'll just have to kill you.
I'll just have to kill you.
Pockwongstar!
Now, it's ice time.
No, it's not lunch yet, Admiral.
What I'm talking about is Portgus D. Ace's execution.
I know that, kid. I was joking. Don't be so uptight.
Please hurry, sir.
Oh, they're summoning us at noon, huh?
They could have at least let us eat our lunch first.
Unruled Kizaru.
Zoro!
Ah!
Who? Who are you? Uh, what are you?
Whatever. Just get the hell away from Zoro!
Oh, no, no. Zoro!
He got hit by one of those laser beams!
Kizaru?
Hey, Usopp! Be careful!
That man's a Navy Admiral!
An admiral!
Uh-oh!
Well, you'll have plenty of time to rest up now.
Zoro!
Crap! He shoots beams, too?
How are we supposed to beat these guys?
At point blank like that, he's done for!
Zoro's in trouble! Come on, do something, guys!
Get away from him! Back up or else!
Take this!
What the hell? Why?
What is this? What's happening?
I can't hit him!
I... I can't stab him!
What the... What can we do?
Trying? Damn it!
Get back! Move your butt!
I mean it!
Leave him alone!
Step away from our friend!
You're wasting your time.
I ate the Glinkland fruit,
and now I'm made of light.
It's a Logia, you see.
He's made of light?
This is a nightmare.
There's nothing we can do.
Zoro! Try to run away!
Now, Van Taflu!
Huh?
It's cute how your friends want to save you,
but you're far beyond help now.
Well then,
time to die.
You picked some time to come out of hiding.
You sure you want to do this, Dark King Rayleigh?
Rayleigh!
Don't go picking these buds before they sprout.
Their era is only just beginning,
and I want to see what they do with it.
I suppose if Old Whitebeard is on the move,
we must put duty ahead of our appetites, huh?
Also at HQ is the Navy's extreme emissary of justice,
Admiral Aka'inu.
The Navy's greatest warriors,
the three admirals,
and the seven warlords of the sea.
Gathered at Marineford,
this formidable force stands between Luffy and his brother Ace.
It's three hours to the execution.
We have to take the prisoner to the scaffold.
Time to go.
50 warships, 100,000 marines,
seven warlords,
and the three Navy admirals,
Aka'inu, Aokiji, and Kizaru.
The stage is set,
and Fleet Admiral Sengoku reveals a shocking truth
as a battle with Whitebeard moves.
On the next,
One Piece,
ticking down to the time of battle,
the Navy's strongest lineup in position.
Aikuku, King of the Pirates!